Guide to the Mix Collection, 1970-2014 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS.143
Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES XII: 1998, 117453
  - Subseries G: Media, 117474
    - Title: Closer to the Metal in My Mouth, Screened: [1998]; 117680 (Box 49, Folder ID: 143.0014)
      Old number: 98-015
      Director: Corcetti, Angie
    - Title: Organ Cranker, Screened: Unknown; 117679 (Box 49, Folder ID: 143.0015)
      Old number: 98-016
      Director: Foulk, Jon
    - Title: Peckerneck Poet, Screened: [1998]; 117678 (Box 49, Folder ID: 143.0016)
      Old number: 98-017
      Director: Plympton, Bill
      Duration: 75 minutes
    - Title: Birth, Screened: [1998]; 117677 (Box 49, Folder ID: 143.0017)
      Old number: 98-018
      Director: White, Lili
    - Title: Cult of Beauty, Screened: [1998]; 117676 (Box 49, Folder ID: 143.0018)
      Old number: 98-019
      Director: Francis, Dean
    - Title: Suroh: Alien Hitchhiker, Screened: [1998]; 117675 (Box 49, Folder ID: 143.0019)
      Old number: 98-021
      Director: McGuinn, Patrick
      Duration: 80 minutes
    - Title: SPF 2000, Screened: [1998]; 117674 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0020)
      Old number: 98-022
    - Title: Cuerpos de Papel, Screened: [1998, 1999]; 117673 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0021)
      Old number: 98-023
      Director: Cuevas, Ximena
    - Title: Going Down, Screened: [1998]; 117672 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0022)
      Old number: 98-024
      Director: McClelland, Doug and Andre Tardif
    - Title: Virtue, Screened: [1998]; 117671 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0023)
      Old number: 98-026
      Director: Camera Obscura
    - Title: Camera Obscura, Screened: [1998]; 117670 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0024)
      Old number: 98-027
      Director: Pilato, Paula
    - Title: La Besofagia, Screened: [1998]; 117669 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0025)
      Old number: 98-028
      Director: Caponi, Claudia
    - Title: Close to Home, Screened: 1998; 117668 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0026)
      Old number: 98-029
    - Title: Tarot of Berlin, Screened: [1998]; 117667 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0027)
      Old number: 98-030
      Director: Falconer, Eddy
      Duration: [90] minutes
    - Title: Medicine Show, Screened: [1998]; 117666 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0028)
      Old number: 98-031
    - Title: Love Film, Screened: [1998]; 117665 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0029)
      Old number: 98-032
      Director: Silberstein, Gulie
    - Title: Gauze, Screened: [1998]; 117664 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0030)
      Old number: 98-033
      Director: Macahilig, Carol Ann
    - Title: Veridical Simulacrum, Screened: [1998]; 117663 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0031)
      Old number: 98-035
      Director: Silverman, Jonathan
    - Title: Mommie Queerest, Screened: [1998]; 117662 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0032)
      Old number: 98-036
      Director: Seckinger, Beverly
    - Title: Bottom (from the top down), Screened: [1998]; 117661 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0033)
      Old number: 98-038
      Director: Lantz, Michael
    - Title: Surviving Friendly Fire: The Making of a Street Kids Theatre Project, Screened: [1998]; 117660 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0034)
      Old number: 98-039
      Director: Nelson, Todd
    - Title: Go Boys!, Screened: 1998; 117659 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0035)
      Old number: 98-040
      Director: Canonge, Hector
    - Title: Aviator, Screened: 1998; 117658 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0036)
      Old number: 98-042
    - Title: Scent uVa Butch, Screened: [1998]; 117657 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0037)
      Old number: 98-043
      Director: Rosenfeld, Shoshana
    - Title: My Personal Messages, Screened: [1998]; 117656 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0038)
      Old number: 98-044
      Director: Weinberg, Sharri
    - Title: Case Study, Screened: [1998]; 117655 (Box 50, Folder ID: 143.0039)
      Old number: 98-045
      Director: Walton, Jean
    - Title: Giftwrap, Screened: [1998]; 117654 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0040)
      Old number: 98-048
    - Title: Dual Passport, Screened: [1998]; 117653 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0041)
      Old number: 98-050
      Director: Jacobson, Fanny
    - Title: Calypso!, Screened: 1998; 117652 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0042)
      Old number: 98-051
      Director: Hull, Andrew
    - Title: Puri, Screened: 1998; 117651 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0043)
      Old number: 98-0552
      Director: Noorani, Arif and D'Souza, Kevin
    - Title: Guidelines for Accepting Reality, Screened: [1998]; 117650 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0044)
      Old number: 98-054
      Director: Heitner, Devoarh
    - Title: Her Tattoo, Screened: 1998; 117649 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0045)
      Old number: 98-057 57056
      Director: Leban, Lexi
    - Title: [1.]-- Strange Sisters [2.]-- Dyke March '97, Screened: [1.]-- 1998 [2.]-- 1997; 117648 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0046)
      Old number: 98-058 98-059
      Director: Swiergalska, Lilka
    - Title: Crush, Screened: 1998; 117647 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0047)
      Old number: 98-060
    - Title: Window of Opportunity, Screened: [1998]; 117646 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0048)
      Old number: 98-0061
      Director: Gort, Gene
    - Title: People Like Us, Screened: [1998]; 117645 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0049)
      Old number: 98-062
      Director: Popadynetz, Wendy
    - Title: Trophy, Screened: [1998]; 117644 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0050)
      Old number: 98-063
      Director: Bogue, Gaea [Rice, Teri ?]
    - Title: Hotties on Acid, Screened: [1998]; 117643 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0051)
      Old number: 98-064
      Director: Stupak, Bec
    - Title: Red Thread, Screened: [1998]; 117642 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0052)
      Old number: 98-065
      Director: Salvitti, John
    - Title: Video Pool Gay and Lesbian Preview Compilation: [1.]-- Homogeneity [2.]-- Pocahontas [3.]-- Working Baby Dyke Theory [4.]-- Colonization [5.]-- Puri [6.]-- Valkyrie Theory [7.]-- Kissy Suziki Suck [8.]-- Water into Fire [9.]-- The Headless Woman, Screened: [1998]; 117641 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0053)
      Old number: 98-068 98-069 98-070 98-071 98-072 98-073 98-074 98-075
      Director: [1.]-- Millan, Lori and Shawna Dempsey [2.]-- Tam, Ho [3.]-- Cuthand, Thirza [4.]-- Cuthand, Thirza [5.]-- D'Souza, Kevin and Arif Noorani [6.]-- Bristol, Joanne [7.]-- Murray, Alison [8.]-- Longboy, Zachery [9.]-- Millan, Lori and Shawna Dempsey
    - Title: Dancing Under the Bombs, Screened: [1998]; 117640 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0054)
      Old number: 98-076
      Director: Vallois, Phillippe
    - Title: Strait, Screened: 1998; 117639 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0055)
      Old number: 98-077
    - Title: 10m Freestyle, Screened: [1998]; 117638 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0056)
      Old number: 98-078
    - Title: Second Time, Screened: [1998]; 117637 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0057)
      Old number: 98-079
    - Title: Guerita and Prietita, Screened: [1998]; 117636 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0058)
      Old number: 98-081
      Director: High, Kathy and Mootoo, Shani
    - Title: Wipe, Screened: [1998]; 117635 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0059)
      Old number: 98-082
      Director: Lang, Paul
    - Title: [1.]-- Condola [2.]-- Sad Story of a Gay Skater, Screened: [1998]; 117634 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0060)
      Old number: 98-083
      Director: Topham, Geoffrey and Jonathan Wells
    - Title: Maureen Bradley Preview Compilation: [1.]-- Forever [2.]-- Losing It [3.]-- HER, Screened: [1998]; 117633 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0061)
      Old number: 98-084
    - Title: Laurel Swenson Preview Compilation 1995-96: [1.]-- Mother Fuckers [2.]-- Your Mother Wears Combat Boots [3.]-- Fistfull, Screened: [1998]; 117632 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0062)
      Old number: 98-085
      Director: Swenson, Laurie
    - Title: In Living Memory, Screened: [1998]; 117631 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0063)
      Old number: 98-086
    - Title: Star Trek: Disco Generation, Screened: [1998]; 117630 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0064)
      Old number: 98-087
      Director: Wong, Gordon
    - Title: Remotely in Touch, Screened: [1998]; 117629 (Box 51, Folder ID: 143.0065)
      Old number: 98-088
      Director: Laiwan
    - Title: Remotely in Touch, Screened: [1998]; 117628 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0066)
    - Title: Transmission, Screened: 1998; 117627 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0067)
      Old number: 98-089
      Director: Coyote, Ivan E.
    - Title: The Subtler Matter, Screened: 1998; 117626 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0068)
      Old number: 98-091
      Director: Devereaux, Emile
      Duration: 23 minutes
    - Title: The Holy Body Tattoo: Poetry and Apocalypse, Screened: [1998]; 117625 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0069)
      Old number: 98-092
      Director: Gagnon, Noam and Dana Gingras and William Morrison and Valeria Nelson
      Duration: 32 minutes
    - Title: Works by Stuart Gaffney: Sex Offender, Screened: [1998]; 117624 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0070)
      Old number: 98-093 98-094 98-095 98-096 98-097
    - Title: Hardhead Flair, Screened: 1998; 117623 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0071)
      Old number: 98-098
      Director: Yeomans, Erika
    - Title: [1.]--Sisyphus and the Scientists [2.]-- The Cock Fight, Screened: [1998]; 117622 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0072)
      Old number: 98-099
      Director: DiLillo, Lisa
    - Title: Boy Next Door, Screened: [1998]; 117621 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0073)
      Old number: 98-100
      Director: Pfirman, Carl
    - Title: Slow Dance, Screened: [1998]; 117620 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0074)
      Old number: 98-101
    - Title: Honey Moccasin (Preview Copy), Screened: [1998]; 117619 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0075)
      Old number: 98-102
      Director: Niro, Shelley
    - Title: Lez B Friends: A Biker Bitch Hate Story, Screened: 1998; 117618 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0076)
      Old number: 98-105
      Director: Steak, Uncle and Lou, Auntie
    - Title: Fraternity, Screened: [1998]; 117617 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0077)
      Old number: 98-106
      Director: Harbin, Sarah
    - Title: Happiness in Florianopolis, Screened: [1998]; 117616 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0078)
      Old number: 98-107
      Director: Bernardo, Aglair
    - Title: Dance Dance Dance, Screened: [1998]; 117615 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0079)
      Old number: 98-108
      Director: Chen, Ming-Lang
    - Title: Cinenova Lesbian Showreel: [1.]-- Monomyth [2.]-- Memory Tracks [3.]-- Killing Time [4.]-- Naya Zamana [5.]-- Wavelengths [6.]-- After the Break [7.]-- Rash [8.]-- Swollen Stigma [9.]-- Impact Zone [10.]-- Dual Passport, Screened: [1998]; 117614 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0080)
      Old number: 98-109 98-110 98-111 98-112 98-113 98-114 98-115 98-116
      Director: [1.]-- Ara, Rachael [2.]-- Ajalon, Jamika [3.]-- T, Esther [4.]-- Rupa, Mandrika [5.]-- Parmar, Pratibha [6.]-- Kennerley, Annette [7.]-- Smith, Vicky [8.]-- Pucill, Sarah [9.]-- Kuhne, Kadet and Sophie Constantinou [10.]-- Jacobson, Fanny
    - Title: Cinenova Transgender Showreel: [1.]-- Boys in the Backyard [2.]-- Kelby [3.]-- Norrie, Screened: [1998]; 117613 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0081)
      Old number: 98-117 98-118 98-119
    - Title: God Shave the Queen, Screened: [1998]; 117612 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0082)
      Old number: 98-124
      Director: [Kashanki, Richard]
    - Title: Rubber Gloves, Screened: 1998; 117611 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0083)
      Director: Brown, Tom E.
    - Title: [1.]--Shrubbery – Another Beautiful Thing [2.]-- Porno Movie, Screened: [1998]; 117610 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0084)
      Old number: 98-127 98-128
      Director: Bull, Marilyn
    - Title: [1.]--Soul Attack [2.]-- Techno Trance World [3.]-- Meditation, Screened: [1998]; 117609 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0085)
      Old number: 98-129
      Director: Ackerman, Larry
    - Title: 2408: A Year Living in the Gertrude Stein House, Screened: [1998]; 117608 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0086)
      Old number: 98-130
      Director: Ferrara, Gin
    - Title: We Can't All Have Come from That Island in Greece, Screened: [1998]; 117607 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0087)
      Old number: 98-131 V107
      Director: Szajko, Lidia
    - Title: Horrorhead, Screened: [1998]; 117606 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0088)
      Old number: 98-132
      Director: Gray, Stephanie and Kelly Spivey
    - Title: Untitled (My Parents Read Dreams I've Had About Them), Screened: 1998; 117605 (Box 52, Folder ID: 143.0089)
      Old number: 98-133
    - Title: Trance, Screened: [1998]; 117604 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0090)
      Old number: 98-134
      Director: Corzine, George
    - Title: Virgin of the Sea, Screened: [1998]; 117603 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0091)
      Old number: 98-135
      Director: Russo, Christine J.
    - Title: Untitled, Screened: [1998]; 117602 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0092)
      Old number: 98-136
      Director: Power, Andrew
    - Title: Barney Frankly on E.N.D.A, Screened: [1998]; 117601 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0093)
      Old number: 98-139
    - Title: Black and White, Screened: [1998]; 117600 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0094)
      Old number: 98-141
      Director: Byrd, Jeffery
    - Title: Life-Size, Screened: [1998]; 117599 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0095)
      Old number: 98-146
    - Title: posiTiVe, Screened: [1998]; 117598 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0096)
      Old number: 98-148
      Director: Scully, Patrick and Eric Gupton
      Duration: 53 minutes
    - Title: Lycanthrophobia, Screened: 1998; 117597 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0097)
      Old number: 98-149 31366
      Director: Victor, Harry
    - Title: Meninas, Screened: 1998; 117596 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0098)
      Director: Alves, Paula
    - Title: Cache, Screened: 1998; 117595 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0099)
      Old number: 98-151
      Director: Coal, Carolyn
    - Title: Suspension, Screened: 1998; 117594 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0100)
      Old number: 98-153
      Director: Phillips, David and Rowley, Paul
    - Title: Lisa Lisa, Screened: [1998]; 117593 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0101)
      Old number: 98-154
      Director: Levin, Melissa
    - Title: The Lesbian Tapes (After Illene Segalove), Screened: [1998]; 117592 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0102)
      Old number: 98-155
    - Title: Dysfunctional, Screened: [1998]; 117591 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0103)
      Old number: 98-156
      Director: Ross, Mirha-Soleil
    - Title: [1.]-- Dysfunctional Premiere at ART Gig Apr '97 [2.]-- Dysfunctional @ Carnival Perversions June '98, Screened: [1998]; 117590 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0104)
    - Title: The Words Are Falling Out of Her Head, Screened: [1998]; 117589 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0105)
      Old number: 98-157
      Director: Gray, Stephanie
    - Title: Bog, Screened: [1998]; 117588 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0106)
      Old number: 98-158
      Director: Spanos, Timothy
      Duration: [180] minutes
    - Title: Basement, Screened: 1998; 117587 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0107)
      Old number: 98-159
      Director: Mau, Heidi
    - Title: IFTI, Screened: [1998]; 117586 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0108)
      Old number: 98-160
      Director: Majid, Hajira
    - Title: Sororocide, Screened: [1998]; 117585 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0109)
      Old number: 98-162
      Director: Cottis, Jane
    - Title: Xin Lu: A Travelogue in Four Parts, Part One: Myth(s) of Creation, Screened: 1998; 117584 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0110)
      Old number: 98-163
    - Title: Tattu, Screened: 1998; 117583 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0111)
      Old number: 98-164
      Director: Roethlein, Terry
      Distributor: performers: [listed in 1998 program]
    - Title: Loki, Screened: [1998]; 117582 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0112)
      Old number: 98-165
      Director: Simon, Peter and Anselm Weidman
    - Title: Untitled (Guide), Screened: [1998]; 117581 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0113)
      Old number: 98-166
      Director: Fedde, RA
    - Title: Head Shot, Screened: [1998]; 117580 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0114)
      Old number: 98-167
      Director: Chomont, Tom
    - Title: Estrofemme, Screened: [1998]; 117579 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0115)
      Old number: 98-170
      Director: Mah, Leslie
    - Title: Goodnight I Love You, Screened: [1998]; 117578 (Box 53, Folder ID: 143.0116)
      Old number: 98-171
      Director: Thomas, Gordon
    - Title: Revelation, Screened: 1998; 117577 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0117)
      Old number: 98-172
      Director: Machens, Scott
    - Title: Sando to Samantha (aka the art of dikvel), Screened: [1998]; 117576 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0118)
      Old number: 98-173
      Director: Lewis, Jack and Thulanie Phungula
    - Title: OK, Screened: [1998]; 117575 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0119)
      Old number: 98-174
    - Title: Charles Impossible Ford, Screened: [1998]; 117574 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0120)
      Old number: 98-176
      Director: Kalmbach, Heiko
    - Title: Anti-Suicide Note, Screened: [1998]; 117573 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0121)
      Old number: 98-177
      Director: Spivey, Katherine
    - Title: Paragenoiacide, Screened: [1998]; 117572 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0122)
      Old number: 98-178
      Director: Beavers, Brent
    - Title: Such Candor, Screened: [1998]; 117571 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0123)
      Old number: 98-179
      Director: Siegel, Marc
    - Title: Gay Shame '98, Screened: 1998; 117570 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0124)
      Old number: 98-187
      Director: Berry, Scott
    - Title: These Are a Few of My Favorite Things, Screened: 1998; 117569 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0125)
      Old number: 98-188
      Director: Hoang, Nguyen Tan
    - Title: [1.]-- Eerie [2.]-- Night Dances, Screened: [1998]; 117568 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0126)
      Old number: 98-189 98-190
      Director: Lahire, Sandra
    - Title: Hidden Child, Screened: 1998; 117567 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0127)
      Old number: 98-191
      Director: Whitley, Brian
    - Title: I Can't Get Her Out of My Mouth, Screened: [1998]; 117566 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0128)
      Old number: 98-192
      Director: Mentlik, Gail and Anne Borden
    - Title: The Great Bravura, Screened: [1998]; 117565 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0129)
      Old number: 98-193
      Director: Dearman, Jill
    - Title: It Dwells in Mirrors, Screened: [1998]; 117564 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0130)
      Old number: 98-203
    - Title: Positiv, Screened: 1998; 117563 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0210)
      Old number: 98-206
    - Title: Shoulda… Coulda… Woulda…, Screened: 1998; 117562 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0211)
      Old number: 98-207
    - Title: Eyediom Filmatelier, Screened: 1998; 117561 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0212)
      Old number: 98-208, 98-209, 98-210
    - Title: Child-Play, Screened: 1998; 117560 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0213)
      Old number: 98-211
    - Title: Yearbook, Screened: 1998; 117559 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0214)
      Old number: 98-213
      Director: Thorne, Kiki
    - Title: St. Francis of Aztlan, Screened: 1998; 117558 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0215)
      Old number: 98-215
      Director: Gonzalez, Rita
    - Title: Jules, Screened: 1998; 117557 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0216)
      Old number: 98-216
      Director: Steinberg, Abigail
    - Title: Even Stephen, Screened: 1998; 117556 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0217)
      Old number: 98-217
      Director: Green, Mary-Pat
    - Title: Movie, Screened: 1998; 117555 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0218)
      Old number: 98-218
    - Title: When Is a Political Movement Like a Sexual Fantasy?, Screened: 1998; 117554 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0219)
      Old number: 98-219
      Director: Moser, Dana
    - Title: Meanwhile, In…, Screened: 1998; 117553 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0220)
      Old number: 98-220
      Director: Duriaud, Aline
    - Title: Borne Again, Screened: 1998; 117552 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0221)
      Old number: 98-221
    - Title: Spiritual Animal Kingdom '27, Screened: 1998; 117551 (Box 54, Folder ID: 143.0222)
      Old number: 98-225
    - Title: And Then the Dog Came Over…, Screened: 1998; 117550 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0223)
      Old number: 98-229
      Director: Sitty, Rebekah
    - Title: Miracle Now, Screened: 1998; 117549 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0224)
      Old number: 98-230
      Director: [THE JOHNSONS/ Antony Hegarty]
    - Title: Jon Benet Goes to Nazi Germany, Screened: 1998; 117548 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0225)
      Old number: 98-231
      Director: Bowery 2000
    - Title: The Grace of God, Screened: 1998; 117547 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0226)
      Old number: 98-241
      Director: L'Ecuyer, Gerald
    - Title: Cat Swallows Parakeet and Speaks!, Screened: 1998; 117546 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0227)
      Old number: 98-255
      Director: Pietrobruno, Ileana
    - Title: Sweetmeats Demo Reel, Screened: 1998; 117545 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0228)
      Old number: 98-258
      Director: Oppenheimer, Joshua
    - Title: The Entire History of the Louisiana Purchase, Screened: 1998; 117544 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0229)
      Old number: 98-259
    - Title: Up and Away with the Meeps, Screened: 1998; 117543 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0230)
      Old number: 98-261
      Director: Donahue, Sarah L.
    - Title: Hide and Seek, Screened: 1998, 1996; 117542 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0231)
      Old number: 98-263
      Director: Walker, Philip
    - Title: Pooneet's Search, Screened: 1998; 117541 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0232)
      Old number: 98-264
      Director: Yuan, Peipei
    - Title: Rocket Girl's Revenge, Screened: 1998; 117540 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0233)
      Old number: 98-265
      Director: Holch, Meredith E.
    - Title: I Got the Red, Screened: 1998; 117539 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0234)
      Old number: 98-266
      Director: Holch, Meredith
    - Title: My Hero, Screened: 1998; 117538 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0235)
      Old number: 98-267
    - Title: Susie and Maria, Screened: 1998; 117537 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0236)
      Old number: 98-268
    - Title: Edited for TV, Collage Films: [1.]-- Jonathan Culp! [2.]-- Our Vacation Trip [3.]-- Chew it, Somalia! [4.]-- The Boob [6.]-- Action! [7.]-- Landescapes [8.]-- Down with Fun, Screened: 1998; 117536 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0237)
      Old number: 98-275
      Director: Culp, Jonathan
    - Title: Destroying Angel, Screened: [1998]; 117535 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0238)
      Old number: 98-277
      Director: Salazar, Wayne and Hoffman, Philip
    - Title: Tick, Tick, Screened: 1998; 117534 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0239)
      Old number: 98-278
      Director: Smith, Paul
    - Title: The Sacred Heart, Screened: 1998; 117533 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0240)
      Old number: 98-280
      Director: Vekie, Natalija
    - Title: Chocolate Is an Indian Word: [1.]-- Bindi on My Nose [2.]-- Yellow [3.]-- Beetle Blues [4.]-- Bindi the Fish, Screened: 1998; 117532 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0241)
      Old number: 98-281, 98-282, 98-283, 98-284
      Director: Gitanjali and Beharry, Shauna
    - Title: [1.]--Who Calcutta the Cheese [2.]--One Ration Under God [3.]--The Booby Trap [4.]--Common Cents [5.]--Radioactive Crotchman [6.]--Beat the Meatl, Screened: 1998; 117531 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0242)
      Old number: 98-285, 98-286, 98-287, 98-288, 98-289, 98-290
      Director: DNA Productions, Inc.
    - Title: Division, Screened: 1998; 117530 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0243)
      Old number: 98-291
      Director: Nadeau, GM
    - Title: Krazy Girls!, Screened: 1998; 117529 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0244)
      Old number: 98-292
      Director: Wylie, Jeff
    - Title: Viens, Mallika…, Screened: 1998; 117528 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0245)
      Old number: 98-294
      Director: Quince, Donna
    - Title: My Own Face Opposite, Screened: 1998; 117527 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0246)
      Old number: 98-295
      Director: Gjestvang, Liv
    - Title: [1.]--Consensual $ex [2.]--The Death of Sex in NYC, Screened: 1998; 117526 (Box 55, Folder ID: 143.0247)
      Old number: 98-296, 98-297
      Director: [Ho, Jennifer M.S.]
    - Title: Hallelujah!, Screened: [1998]; 117525 (Box 56, Folder ID: 143.0149)
      Old number: 98-046
      Director: Saalfield, Catherine